Problem D - Maximum Product

Time Limit: 1 second

Given a sequence of integers S = {S1, S2, ..., Sn}, you should determine what is the value of the maximum positive product involving consecutive terms of S. If you cannot find a positive sequence, you should consider 0 as the value of the maximum product.

Input

Each test case starts with 1 ≤ N ≤ 18, the number of elements in a sequence. Each element Si is an integer such that -10 ≤ Si ≤ 10. Next line will have N integers, representing the value of each element in the sequence. There is a blank line after each test case. The input is terminated by end of file (EOF).

Output

For each test case you must print the message: Case #M: The maximum product is P., where M is the number of the test case, starting from 1, and P is the value of the maximum product. After each test case you must print a blank line.

Sample Input

3
2 4 -3

5
2 5 -1 2 -1

Sample Output

Case #1: The maximum product is 8.

Case #2: The maximum product is 20.
